https://www.rmbi.org.uk/terms-conditions/

MenuRMBI
Close
SafetyOur Homes Our HomesWellbeing StatementTypes of CareVolunteeringApply for Care Apply for CareYour Care ChecklistNews News and StoriesIn Their WordsRMBI NewsDementia ZoneCareers CareersCurrent VacanciesJob RolesLearning and DevelopmentReward and BenefitsVolunteeringAbout Us About UsOur PeopleOur Impact ReportContact Us
Login Contact UsEnglish Cymraeg Search for:
Home | Terms & ConditionsTerms and conditionsPrivacy StatementAt RMBI Care Co. we are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. If you provide personal information we will only ever use this to send you information relating to RMBI Care Co. that you have requested to receive from us. We strive to ensure that this website is monitored effectively to prevent possible breaches of any individual privacy.Any information given by you to RMBI Care Co. will be used solely for the purpose for which it was given and we will continue to request consent on a regular basis. You can withdraw consent at any time by sending an email to marketing@rmbi.org.uk or by writing to RMBI Marketing, 60 Great Queen Street, London WC2B 5AZ.We will not share your information with any third parties or store your details outside of the European Economic Area.  The information you provide will be held securely by us whether the information is in electronic or physical format.DisclaimerRMBI Care Co.’s website contains hyperlinks to many other websites. This information is supplied in good faith, in case it is of interest or use to RMBI Care Co. website users. RMBI Care Co. is not responsible for the content or functionality of any of these external websites (although please let us know if a link is not working by emailing marketing@rmbi.org.uk)Any access to another site from this site is independent of RMBI Care Co. RMBI Care Co. has no control over the content of other sites and has not endorsed or approved the content of such sites.You should be aware that if an external website requests personal information from you (for example, in connection with an order for goods or services), this information is supplied to, stored and used by the company concerned, and that RMBI care Co. will not be liable to you or any other person for loss or damage directly or indirectly for any use of this or any site linked to it.Legal messageThe information on this website has been provided as general information only. RMBI Care Co. cannot accept responsibility for loss occasioned after reliance placed on any of the contents of this website. RMBI Care Co. makes no warranty as to the accuracy of site information or contents.Your use of RMBI Care Co.’s website is governed by the conditions below and passing beyond the homepage is deemed as acceptance of these conditions.Website visitors aged under 16If you are aged under 16, please ensure that you obtain your parent’s or guardian’s consent before sending any personal information to this website, including any information required for downloading our publications. Please note that RMBI Care Co. will not accept online donations or membership subscriptions from persons aged under 16 years.Copyright and reproductionsAll page content made available on this website is Copyright © 2018 RMBI Care Co. unless otherwise stated.All photographs are Copyright © 2018 RMBI Care Co. or their individual owner unless otherwise stated.The site may contain other propriety notices and copyright information, the terms of which must be observed and followed.You may download to a local hard disk and print extracts from this site for personal use and information. You can duplicate the information for the personal use of others only. Information is not to be copied to use in any other website, database or publication or any other form of work.Please contact RMBI Care Co. if you wish to use a photograph or any information given, for incorporation into any form of publication medium, or for any use other than private viewing.CookiesA cookie is a very small text file placed on your computer’s hard drive (by the website server) when you visit certain web pages. It is associated with the computer that you are using and it cannot deliver viruses. RMBI Care Co.’s website uses some cookies – for example, cookies are used to save you from entering your data on multiple occasions when downloading more than one publication. If you disable the use of cookies in your browser, we cannot guarantee that all parts of the site will work.Changes to our TermsThe information, material and content provided in the pages of this site may be changed at any time without notice. Changes may be made to the Terms at any time without notice by updating this posting.You agree to review the Terms regularly and your continued access to or use of the site will mean that you agree to any changes. AccessibilityPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsCookie PolicyModern Slavery StatementSustainabilityGender Pay Gap Report Website by Ave Design Studiowhois: Andy White Freelance WordPress Developer London
Skip to content
Open toolbar
Accessibility Tools
Increase Text
Decrease Text
Grayscale
High Contrast
Negative Contrast
